

# Senior Designer, Art Director

I'm a designer and visual thinker, who enjoys creating and developing playful, engaging, interactive solutions. With over five years of experience designing for a variety of industries, including media and entertainment, healthcare, and finance, I've honed my ability to adapt my design aesthetic to a range of brands and styles. An ambitious and quick learner with boundless imagination, I am always excited to take on the next challenge, and to explore its creative possibilities.

## experience

#### Isobar

# Visual Designer New York, NY

Jan 2015 - Aug 2016

- Concepted and designed responsive websites, cross-platform mobile & TV apps (iOS, Android, AppleTV), consumer and internal-facing applications, presentations, pitches, and case studies.
- Conducted market research and concepted solutions to client briefs, representing them through selfdirected moodboards and comps.
- Worked closely with UX designers and developers.
- Performed design QA to ensure products stay on-brand and true to design.
- Clients included NBC (USA, Bravo, Syfy, Telemundo, E!, Esquire, NBC Universo, Oxygen, Sprout, MSNBC), IntegraMed, LexMar Global, and Umpqua Bank.
- Actively attended conferences and workshops to stay on top of design and tech industry trends.
- Led monthly company-wide communications training group.

#### Situation Interactive

#### Interactive Designer New York, NY

May 2013 - Aug 2014

- Concepted and designed websites, landing pages, banners, rich media units, and social media campaigns.
- Storyboarded and developed flash banners, animations, and videos.
- Gave art direction to freelance designers.
- Performed design QA to ensure products stay on-brand and true to design.
- Worked closely with front-end developers, project managers, and account teams.
- Clients included The Metropolitan Opera, Roundabout Theatre, Ripley's Believe It or Not!, and Broadway musicals Wicked, Cinderella, Rock of Ages, Mama Mia!, Beautiful, Hedwig and the Angry Inch, and others.

## **GAIN Capital**

## Interactive Designer Bedminster, NJ

Jun 2012 - May 2013

- Concepted and designed flash banners, landing pages, widgets, infographics, social media assets, and style guides for FOREX.com and GAIN Capital.
- Managed the front-end development of FOREX.com landing pages and the TradeKing Forex microsite.
- Branded TradeKing trading platforms and mobile apps.
- Branded the Tradable for FOREX.com appstore.

## Zemoga

Graphic Design Intern New York, NY

Jun 2011 - Aug 2011

- Concepted and designed on-brand materials, including a laptop case, notepads, and coffee packaging.
- Concepted and designed the Pixels & Pills blog and YouTube assets.

# DoSomething.org

Graphic Design Intern New York, NY

Jan 2011 - Apr 2011

- Concepted and designed wireframes, landing pages, and digital and print collateral for campaigns.
- Campaigns included "Stop Bullying" campaign, Aeropostale's "Teens for Jeans," HP's "Green Your School Challenge," and VH1's "Battle for the Bands."
- Created branding system for DoSomething.org's young social entrepreneur program BootCampX.

## Nimli

Graphic Design Intern New York, NY

Nov 2009 - Feb 2010

- Concepted and designed banners and hero images.
- Retouched product photos for website.

#### education

## **Pratt Institute**

M.S. Communications Design with Digital Design Emphasis

Honored as Distinguished Student New York, NY | May 2012

# Carnegie Mellon University

B.H.A. Fine Arts & Creative and Professional Writing, with Honors

Minor in Business Administration Pittsburgh, PA | May 2009

## honors

- Hilson Family Scholarship Award for Excellence, 2011
- American Assocation of Advertising Agencies Award, Operation Jumpstart Scholarship III Recipient, 2010 - 2011
- National Honors Scholar Society, 2009
- Dean's List, 2008 2009

## skills

## Design

- Art Direction
- Branding
- Concept Development
- Illustration
- UI
- Wireframing
- Responsive Design
- Marketing
- Motion
- Photography
- Packaging
- Print

#### Software

- Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, AfterEffects
- Sketch, InVision
- FinalCut Pro
- Keynote

#### Code

• HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript